Adam Weitzman

C#/Angular/SQL Developer

As a former biology and physics teacher; I'm interested in the intersection of education, technology, and any experience that meshes the digital with the real. I love solving mindwarping code problems with minimalist code and a nice hot cup of tea.



hackturalist.com



Austin



adamcweitzman@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/adamweitzman



4156900695



@hackturalist

Experiences

May 2016 - Present

C#/Front-End Developer - Jackrabbit

- Built Ruby On Rails app with Angular client
- Configured .NET gateway app for MS SDK
- Grid FE with Angular Material and Bootstrap Nov 2015 - May 2016

.NET/SQL Developer - Tripchamp

- Back-end data transformation and serializtion/deserialization in C#
- Used AJAX and NUnit testing along with classic OOP programming
- Set-up custom Load Balancer in AWS to scale project from small-startup to multinational company (India, England) C#.NET MVC App with custom normalization code to map API agents

Awards

2015

3rd place at Lowes Digital Challenge Ionic, Angular, Node – Austin

Education

2008 - 2012

Biological Anthropology/Literature University of Colorado at Boulder Boulder, CO

Aug 2015 - Nov 2015 Web Development Immersive General Assembly Austin, TX

Projects

Doctor Location App http://serene-coast-7290.herokuapp.com Node, Angular, Leaflet, Mapbox, JQuery, MongoDB

GAJobsATX

http://www.gajobsatx.com Node, Angular, Bootstrap, Firebase

Asteroid Defender

https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/new---c---game---adam---weitzman?trk=prof---post C#, Unity, Javascript, 3D Models

RecordKeeper

https://powerful-taiga-9352.herokuapp.com Ruby on Rails, PSQL, Bootstrap

Tools

Mac OS X
.NET
Sketch
Windows 10
Postman
Fiddler
Git
SQL MStudio

Back End Skills

.NET, C# MySQL, PSQL, SQLite Node Ruby on Rails MongoDB, DocDB AWS/Azure



Front End Skills

Angular HTML, CSS LESS, SASS, JSON Material, Bootstrap Javascript, jQuery Git, XML

Hobies













